Yesterday was about honor. Today is about justice.
Shooter is a drama, action, thriller film directed by Antoine Fuqua.
A top Marine sniper, Bob Lee Swagger, leaves the military after a mission
goes horribly awry and disappears, living in seclusion.
He is coaxed back into service after a high-profile government official convinces
him to help thwart a plot to kill the President of the United States.
Ultimately double-crossed and framed for the attempt, Swagger
becomes the target of a nationwide manhunt.
He goes on the run to track the real killer and find out who exactly set him up, and why, eventually
seeking revenge against some of the most powerful and corrupt leaders in the free world.
Bob Lee Swagger, played by Mark Wahlberg.
Nick Memphis, played by Michael Peña.
Colonel Isaac Johnson, played by Danny Glover.
Sarah Fenn, played by Kate Mara.
Jack Payne, played by Elias Koteas.
Alourdes Galindo, played by Rhona Mitra.
Shooter is a 2007 American action thriller film directed by Antoine Fuqua and written by
Jonathan Lemkin, based on the 1993 novel Point of Impact by Stephen Hunter.
The film follows Force Recon Marine Scout Sniper veteran Bob Lee Swagger (Mark Wahlberg), who
is framed for murder by a mercenary unit operating for a private military firm.
The film also stars Michael Peña, Danny Glover, Kate
Mara, Levon Helm, and Ned Beatty.
Shooter was produced by Lorenzo di Bonaventura through Di Bonaventura Pictures, and
released by Paramount Pictures in the United States on March 23, 2007.
The film received mixed reviews and grossed $95.7
million on a $61 million budget.
The film explores themes of philadelphia, pennsylvania,
assassination, usa president, based on novel or book, widow.
The tone is emotional and intense.